[{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Throughput?","choices":[{"id":33,"text":"p3","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":32,"text":"perfo","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":31,"text":"p2","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":30,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Error_Rate?","choices":[{"id":73,"text":"p3","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":72,"text":"perfo","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":71,"text":"p2","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":70,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Jitter?","choices":[{"id":169,"text":"p3","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":168,"text":"perfo","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":167,"text":"p2","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":166,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Latency?","choices":[{"id":188,"text":"p3","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":187,"text":"perfo","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":186,"text":"p2","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":185,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Interplay_Factors?","choices":[{"id":284,"text":"p3","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":283,"text":"perfo","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":282,"text":"p2","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":281,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Bandwidth?","choices":[{"id":378,"text":"p3","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":377,"text":"perfo","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":376,"text":"p2","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":375,"text":"bw","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Congession?","choices":[{"id":540,"text":"p3","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":539,"text":"perfo","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":538,"text":"p2","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":537,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Computer_Networks?","choices":[{"id":869,"text":"p3","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":868,"text":"perfo","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":867,"text":"p2","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":866,"text":"sec","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":865,"text":"scope","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":864,"text":"n1","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Security?","choices":[{"id":954,"text":"availabilty","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":953,"text":"modi","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":952,"text":"confid","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":951,"text":"integ","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":950,"text":"interrr","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":949,"text":"sec","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Scope?","choices":[{"id":1117,"text":"s1","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1116,"text":"s2","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1115,"text":"s3","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1114,"text":"s4","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1113,"text":"scope","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which one of the following response pairs are related ?","choices":[{"id":1691,"text":"Application\tuses\tRADIUS","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":1692,"text":"Network\tuses\tRADIUS","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1693,"text":"ISO_Standard\tuses\tRADIUS","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1694,"text":"Data_Link\tuses\tRADIUS","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which one of the following response pairs are related ?","choices":[{"id":1695,"text":"Internet_Society\tcommittee\tIAB","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":1696,"text":"eMail\tcommittee\tIAB","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1697,"text":"VOIP\tcommittee\tIAB","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1698,"text":"RFC\tcommittee\tIAB","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":1711,"text":"ATM_Layer is  Open Systems Interconnection","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1710,"text":"Switched is  Open Systems Interconnection","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1709,"text":"SVOIP is  Open Systems Interconnection","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1708,"text":"Scope is  Open Systems Interconnection","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1707,"text":"Infrared is  Open Systems Interconnection","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1706,"text":"Bonded_TP is  Open Systems Interconnection","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1705,"text":"IP_Suite is  Open Systems Interconnection","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1704,"text":"Loaded_TP is  Open Systems Interconnection","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1703,"text":"CISCO_IOS is  Open Systems Interconnection","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1702,"text":"Star_Mesh is  Open Systems Interconnection","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1701,"text":"Flooders is  Open Systems Interconnection","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1700,"text":"OSI_Model is  Open Systems Interconnection","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":1715,"text":"LDAP is Remote Desktop Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1714,"text":"SDP is Remote Desktop Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1713,"text":"RTSP is Remote Desktop Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1712,"text":"RDP is Remote Desktop Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":1719,"text":"CMAC is Media Gateway Control Protocol (MGCP)","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1718,"text":"DHCP is Media Gateway Control Protocol (MGCP)","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1717,"text":"SMTP is Media Gateway Control Protocol (MGCP)","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1716,"text":"MGCP is Media Gateway Control Protocol (MGCP)","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":1723,"text":"SFTP is Simple Network Management Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1722,"text":"SDM is Simple Network Management Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1721,"text":"SOAP is Simple Network Management Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1720,"text":"SNMP is Simple Network Management Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":1727,"text":"POP1 is Simple Object Access Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1726,"text":"POP2 is Simple Object Access Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1725,"text":"SNMP is Simple Object Access Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1724,"text":"SOAP is Simple Object Access Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":1731,"text":"FHSS is direct sequence spread spectrum","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1730,"text":"SDP is direct sequence spread spectrum","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1729,"text":"SDM is direct sequence spread spectrum","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1728,"text":"DSSS is direct sequence spread spectrum","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":1735,"text":"TLS is  Real Time Streaming Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1734,"text":"FTP is  Real Time Streaming Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1733,"text":"RDP is  Real Time Streaming Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1732,"text":"RTSP is  Real Time Streaming Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":1740,"text":"FTTN is File Transfer Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1739,"text":"FTTC is File Transfer Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1738,"text":"RTSP is File Transfer Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1737,"text":"FTP is File Transfer Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":1744,"text":"POP1 is Voice over Internet Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1743,"text":"SOAP is Voice over Internet Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1742,"text":"POP2 is Voice over Internet Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1741,"text":"VOIP is Voice over Internet Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":1758,"text":"Gnutella is  Building Automation and Control Networks","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1757,"text":"Integrity is  Building Automation and Control Networks","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1756,"text":"Extranet is  Building Automation and Control Networks","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1755,"text":"Bonded_TP is  Building Automation and Control Networks","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1754,"text":"Honeypots is  Building Automation and Control Networks","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1753,"text":"Permanent is  Building Automation and Control Networks","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1752,"text":"Brouter is  Building Automation and Control Networks","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1751,"text":"Bandwidth is  Building Automation and Control Networks","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1750,"text":"Intranet is  Building Automation and Control Networks","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1749,"text":"Telnet is  Building Automation and Control Networks","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1748,"text":"Internet is  Building Automation and Control Networks","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1747,"text":"Ethernet is  Building Automation and Control Networks","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1746,"text":"BACnet is  Building Automation and Control Networks","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":1766,"text":"FTTC is Hypertext Transfer Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1765,"text":"PHP is Hypertext Transfer Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1764,"text":"RTSP is Hypertext Transfer Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1763,"text":"HTTP is Hypertext Transfer Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":1770,"text":"RTSP is SSH File Transfer Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1769,"text":"SOAP is SSH File Transfer Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1768,"text":"SNMP is SSH File Transfer Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1767,"text":"SFTP is SSH File Transfer Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":1774,"text":"SOAP is Session Description Protocol (SDP)","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1773,"text":"SNMP is Session Description Protocol (SDP)","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1772,"text":"RDP is Session Description Protocol (SDP)","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1771,"text":"SDP is Session Description Protocol (SDP)","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":1779,"text":"SSH is frequency hopping spread spectrum","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1778,"text":"NFS is frequency hopping spread spectrum","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1777,"text":"DSSS is frequency hopping spread spectrum","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1776,"text":"FHSS is frequency hopping spread spectrum","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":1783,"text":"FTP is Network News Transfer Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1782,"text":"RTSP is Network News Transfer Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1781,"text":"SNMP is Network News Transfer Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1780,"text":"NNTP is Network News Transfer Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":1789,"text":"DTLS is denial-of-service attack","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1788,"text":"DNS is denial-of-service attack","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1787,"text":"DSSS is denial-of-service attack","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1786,"text":"DOS is denial-of-service attack","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":1793,"text":"SOAP is Simple Mail Transfer Protocol ","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1792,"text":"SNMP is Simple Mail Transfer Protocol ","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1791,"text":"MGCP is Simple Mail Transfer Protocol ","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1790,"text":"SMTP is Simple Mail Transfer Protocol ","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":1799,"text":"BASET2 is  Advanced Research Projects Agency Network","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1798,"text":"BASET4 is  Advanced Research Projects Agency Network","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1797,"text":"BASET is  Advanced Research Projects Agency Network","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1796,"text":"BASETX is  Advanced Research Projects Agency Network","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1795,"text":"BASET is  Advanced Research Projects Agency Network","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1794,"text":"ARPANET is  Advanced Research Projects Agency Network","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":1803,"text":"DTLS is Domain Name System","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1802,"text":"DOS is Domain Name System","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1801,"text":"DSSS is Domain Name System","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1800,"text":"DNS is Domain Name System","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":1807,"text":"DICT is Internet Engineering Task Force","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1806,"text":"IPTV is Internet Engineering Task Force","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1805,"text":"IDEA is Internet Engineering Task Force","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1804,"text":"IETF is Internet Engineering Task Force","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":1815,"text":"SDP is Synchronous Optical Networking (SONET) and Synchronous Digital Hierarchy (SDH)","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1814,"text":"SDM is Synchronous Optical Networking (SONET) and Synchronous Digital Hierarchy (SDH)","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1813,"text":"DSSS is Synchronous Optical Networking (SONET) and Synchronous Digital Hierarchy (SDH)","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1812,"text":"SDH is Synchronous Optical Networking (SONET) and Synchronous Digital Hierarchy (SDH)","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":1819,"text":"SDP is Lightweight Directory Access Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1818,"text":"SOAP is Lightweight Directory Access Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1817,"text":"RDP is Lightweight Directory Access Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1816,"text":"LDAP is Lightweight Directory Access Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":1823,"text":"IMAP is Internet Assigned Numbers Authority","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1822,"text":"IDEA is Internet Assigned Numbers Authority","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1821,"text":"IAB is Internet Assigned Numbers Authority","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1820,"text":"IANA is Internet Assigned Numbers Authority","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":1828,"text":"POP1 is  Point to Point Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1827,"text":"PHP is  Point to Point Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1826,"text":"POP2 is  Point to Point Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1825,"text":"PPP is  Point to Point Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":1832,"text":"SDH is Secure Shell","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1831,"text":"FHSS is Secure Shell","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1830,"text":"DSSS is Secure Shell","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1829,"text":"SSH is Secure Shell","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":1836,"text":"PHP is Post Office Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1835,"text":"SOAP is Post Office Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1834,"text":"POP2 is Post Office Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1833,"text":"POP is Post Office Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":1840,"text":"PHP is Dynamic Host Configuration Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1839,"text":"MGCP is Dynamic Host Configuration Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1838,"text":"RDP is Dynamic Host Configuration Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1837,"text":"DHCP is Dynamic Host Configuration Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":1844,"text":"IAX is Internet Architecture Board","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1843,"text":"IMAP is Internet Architecture Board","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1842,"text":"IANA is Internet Architecture Board","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1841,"text":"IAB is Internet Architecture Board","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":1848,"text":"SSTP is  chirp spread spectrum ","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1847,"text":"FHSS is  chirp spread spectrum ","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1846,"text":"DSSS is  chirp spread spectrum ","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1845,"text":"CSS is  chirp spread spectrum ","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":1854,"text":"SSB is Server Message Block","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1853,"text":"SMTP is Server Message Block","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1852,"text":"SNMP is Server Message Block","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1851,"text":"SMB is Server Message Block","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":1858,"text":"PPTP is Internet Protocol television","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1857,"text":"IETF is Internet Protocol television","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1856,"text":"FTP is Internet Protocol television","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1855,"text":"IPTV is Internet Protocol television","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":1863,"text":"TDM is HyperText Markup Language","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1862,"text":"SMTP is HyperText Markup Language","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1861,"text":"HTTP is HyperText Markup Language","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1860,"text":"HTML is HyperText Markup Language","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":1869,"text":"ZyNOS is  Network Basic Input Output System","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1868,"text":"JUNOS is  Network Basic Input Output System","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1867,"text":"CISCO_IOS is  Network Basic Input Output System","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1866,"text":"Network is  Network Basic Input Output System","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1865,"text":"Direct_DS is  Network Basic Input Output System","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1864,"text":"NetBIOS is  Network Basic Input Output System","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":1873,"text":"DHCP is Dictionary Server Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1872,"text":"IETF is Dictionary Server Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1871,"text":"FTTC is Dictionary Server Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1870,"text":"DICT is Dictionary Server Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":1877,"text":"HMAC is Quadrature amplitude modulation","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1876,"text":"IMAP is Quadrature amplitude modulation","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1875,"text":"CMAC is Quadrature amplitude modulation","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1874,"text":"QAM is Quadrature amplitude modulation","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":1881,"text":"IMAP is Cipher-based message authentication code","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1880,"text":"QAM is Cipher-based message authentication code","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1879,"text":"MGCP is Cipher-based message authentication code","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1878,"text":"CMAC is Cipher-based message authentication code","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":1885,"text":"IPTV is Internet Research Task Force","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1884,"text":"IETF is Internet Research Task Force","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1883,"text":"RTSP is Internet Research Task Force","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1882,"text":"IRTF is Internet Research Task Force","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":1896,"text":"Class_B is aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1895,"text":"Plastics is aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1894,"text":"Cells is aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1893,"text":"Class_F is aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1892,"text":"Class_C is aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1891,"text":"Class_D is aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1890,"text":"Class_Fa is aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1889,"text":"Star_Mesh is aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1888,"text":"Class_E is aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1887,"text":"Wireless is aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1886,"text":"Class_A is aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":1902,"text":"VOIP is Routing Information Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1901,"text":"RTSP is Routing Information Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1900,"text":"RDP is Routing Information Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1899,"text":"RIP is Routing Information Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":1907,"text":"VOIP is Session Initiation Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1906,"text":"SOAP is Session Initiation Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1905,"text":"SNMP is Session Initiation Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1904,"text":"SIP is Session Initiation Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":1911,"text":"MPPE is Multipurpose Internet Mail Extensions","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1910,"text":"IMAP is Multipurpose Internet Mail Extensions","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1909,"text":"IDEA is Multipurpose Internet Mail Extensions","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1908,"text":"MIME is Multipurpose Internet Mail Extensions","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":1917,"text":"TLS is Time hopping spread spectrum ","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1916,"text":"RTSP is Time hopping spread spectrum ","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1915,"text":"DSSS is Time hopping spread spectrum ","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1914,"text":"THSS is Time hopping spread spectrum ","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":1926,"text":"FTTN is Fiber to the x","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1925,"text":"FTP is Fiber to the x","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1924,"text":"FTTC is Fiber to the x","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1923,"text":"FTTX is Fiber to the x","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":1930,"text":"FTP is Trivial File Transfer Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1929,"text":"FTTC is Trivial File Transfer Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1928,"text":"RTSP is Trivial File Transfer Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1927,"text":"TFTP is Trivial File Transfer Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":1934,"text":"SOAP is Internet message access protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1933,"text":"SNMP is Internet message access protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1932,"text":"MGCP is Internet message access protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1931,"text":"IMAP is Internet message access protocol","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":1938,"text":"SNTP is Session Traversal Utilities for NAT","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1937,"text":"SFTP is Session Traversal Utilities for NAT","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1936,"text":"FTTN is Session Traversal Utilities for NAT","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1935,"text":"STUN is Session Traversal Utilities for NAT","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":1942,"text":"RTSP is Active Server Pages","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1941,"text":"SOAP is Active Server Pages","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1940,"text":"SNMP is Active Server Pages","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1939,"text":"ASP is Active Server Pages","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":1946,"text":"SSTP is single sideband modulation","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1945,"text":"SSH is single sideband modulation","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1944,"text":"DSSS is single sideband modulation","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1943,"text":"SSB is single sideband modulation","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":1950,"text":"IANA is wireless local area network","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1949,"text":"LDAP is wireless local area network","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1948,"text":"AAL is wireless local area network","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1947,"text":"WLAN is wireless local area network","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":1955,"text":"HTML is hash message authentication code","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1954,"text":"DHCP is hash message authentication code","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1953,"text":"MGCP is hash message authentication code","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1952,"text":"HMAC is hash message authentication code","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":1959,"text":"IMAP is Inter-Asterisk eXchange (IAX)","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1958,"text":"IAB is Inter-Asterisk eXchange (IAX)","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1957,"text":"IANA is Inter-Asterisk eXchange (IAX)","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1956,"text":"IAX is Inter-Asterisk eXchange (IAX)","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":1966,"text":"RTSP is JavaServer Pages","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1965,"text":"SOAP is JavaServer Pages","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1964,"text":"SNMP is JavaServer Pages","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1963,"text":"JSP is JavaServer Pages","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":1972,"text":"NNTP is NetWare Core Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1971,"text":"SNMP is NetWare Core Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1970,"text":"MGCP is NetWare Core Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1969,"text":"NCP is NetWare Core Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":1976,"text":"FTP is Real-time Transport Protocol (RTP)","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1975,"text":"RTSP is Real-time Transport Protocol (RTP)","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1974,"text":"RDP is Real-time Transport Protocol (RTP)","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1973,"text":"RTP is Real-time Transport Protocol (RTP)","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":1980,"text":"FTP is Network Time Protocol ","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1979,"text":"RTSP is Network Time Protocol ","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1978,"text":"SNMP is Network Time Protocol ","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1977,"text":"NTP is Network Time Protocol ","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":1984,"text":"IP_Suite is Secure Voice over IP","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1983,"text":"CISCO_IOS is Secure Voice over IP","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1982,"text":"OSI_Model is Secure Voice over IP","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1981,"text":"SVOIP is Secure Voice over IP","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":1991,"text":"SMB is space modulation","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1990,"text":"SMTP is space modulation","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1989,"text":"SNMP is space modulation","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":1988,"text":"SM is space modulation","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"}]